Ding Dingdang: How did you find this?
He Heda: Found one of those combination locks.
Jin Jinliang: Are there any key dates for it?
He Heda: It's a three-digit passcode.
Jin Jinliang: Can't we just try 999 times?
Jin Jinliang: Hurry, try it.
Jin Jinliang: 123.
He Heda: Quick, give me some 3-digit codes.
Keke Ai: 777.
Ding Dingdang: I tried 777.
It's time-out now.
Wait three minutes before restarting.
Ning Ninghou: Have you tried 777?
Ding Dingdang: Tried it, I just tried it.
Ning Ninghou: 777 Xingfu Road.
Ding Dingdang: I just tried it.
Ning Ninghou: It's wrong.
He Heda: Four.
Jin Jinliang: 329.
Nan Nandu: 309?
Jin Jinliang: 0309 is also possible.
Ning Ninghou: 309.
Ding Dingdang: It's only three digits.
Jin Jinliang: 309.
Ning Ninghou: 309 is wrong.
Ning Ninghou: 309 is his suicide, right?
Nan Nandu: The day he died.
Ning Ninghou: 309 is wrong.
Nan Nandu: 324, were these here yesterday?
Ning Ninghou: What's 324 for?
Nan Nandu: Four.
Jin Jinliang: 324 seems to be his upload date.
Ning Ninghou: What is 324?
He Heda: When his grandma learned of that
He Heda: news, what date was it?
Jin Jinliang: It was February something.
Nan Nandu: 2024.
Jin Jinliang: No, February 2026.
Ding Dingdang: Whose room is this?
Nan Nandu: His room.
He Heda: His, Li Liwo's.
Jin Jinliang: Strokes in Li Liwo? 1,2,3,4,5,6.
Jin Jinliang: 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7.
Jin Jinliang: Try 667.
Ding Dingdang: Li Liwo.
Ning Ninghou: What is 667?
Nan Nandu: The strokes of his name.
Ning Ninghou: It's wrong.
Ding Dingdang: Then...
Ding Dingdang: Let's try it.
He Heda: How about 250? 250.
Jin Jinliang: Then how about 520?
Ning Ninghou: 520.
Keke Ai: Could you just tell us?
Li Liwo: I definitely don't know.
Keke Ai: I don't think it's outside.
Keke Ai: It should be that combination lock.
Keke Ai: There's a key inside.
Jin Jinliang: Right.
Keke Ai: To open that.
Keke Ai: And then it's over there.
Ning Ninghou: I unboxed a 3-layer package.
Ning Ninghou: And there was nothing inside.
Ning Ninghou: What's related to the number 3?
3.
Jin Jinliang: 618.
He Heda: 308.
Ding Dingdang: Did you check the fridge?
Jin Jinliang: I did, there's nothing.
Keke Ai: No, there's nothing at all.
Jin Jinliang: What's on the fridge magnet?
Jin Jinliang: Take it down and see.
He Heda: It's just a fridge magnet.
Ding Dingdang: I've searched everywhere.
He Heda: I think it should be in here.
He Heda: Or in that one.
Ning Ninghou: Do you think it's here?
Ning Ninghou: There's a key to open that.
He Heda: Could be.
Nan Nandu: Must still be related to him.
He Heda: Could the key be on him?
Jin Jinliang: Doesn't touching him cost 30s?
Keke Ai: Fortune favors the bold, my friend.
He Heda: Right, let's strip him then.
Everyone, stay where you are.
Starting in three minutes.
Jin Jinliang: It's time-out right now.
Ding Dingdang: I'm going back to my spot.
Jin Jinliang: Give him the medicine first.
Jin Jinliang: To quiet him down.
He Heda: Where's the medicine?
Ding Dingdang: Where's the medicine?
Keke Ai: What medicine?
Jin Jinliang: The medicine is in there.
Jin Jinliang: So we need to find the key first.
Jin Jinliang: But we need to search him.
Jin Jinliang: We have to quiet him down.
Jin Jinliang: Let's give him the medicine first.
Keke Ai: We don't need to quiet him down.
Ding Dingdang: Did anyone check up there?
He Heda: Checked.
Keke Ai: I'll just hold him tight.
Li Liwo: It's definitely useless.
Li Liwo: Don't search, it's really useless.
Keke Ai: Really?
Li Liwo: Useless, seriously useless.
Jin Jinliang: We got a chance.
Keke Ai: Where on the sofa was it?
Ding Dingdang: Here.
Jin Jinliang: Found it by moving the sofa.
Ding Dingdang: No.
Ding Dingdang: It wasn't under the sofa.
Ding Dingdang: It was right here.
Ding Dingdang: It was under this.
Once this curtain is pulled open.